

ABOUT ME



08 05 95



De-Billemonstraat 109, 2440 Geel



+32 466 40 45 70



zeeshanmehmood 59640@gmail.com

EXPERTISE SKILL

- React JS
- WordPress
- HTML, CSS/SCSS, BootStrap
- JavaScript
- MySQL, Java
- Python/Fast API
- GitHub, Docker
- Scrum Management / Jira
- Graphic Designing

LANGUAGES

Urdu

English





HOBBIES

success.

Tourism, Book reading, listening to music ...

E - Gaming: E-gaming often involves playing in teams or collaborating with others. Effective teamwork, communication, and coordination are crucial for

ZEESHAN MEHMOOD

Web Developer

A flexible and adaptable Web Developer who approaches coding as an art form, and every project as a masterpiece waiting to happen. My ability to effectively communicate and collaborate with others complements my talent for converting difficult ideas into sophisticated, approachable solutions. I'm passionate about turning ideas into reality and am committed to delivering highquality web experiences that resonate with users and stakeholders alike

EDUCATION

Professional Bachelors Applied Computer Science

2023 - Present, Thomas More Campus Geel Specialization in Artifical Intelligence

Bachelor's in Electrical Engineering

2013 - 2017, National University of Science and Technology, Pakistan

Specialization in Telecommunication and Radars 2.44 GPA

Higher Secondary School Education

2011 - 2013, Kallar Kahar Science College, Pakistan 89 % Marks

EXPERIENCE

Student Job at McDonald's

March 2023 - Sep 2023, McDonald's Geel

Front End Web Development

2021 - 2022, Siginific Web Solutions, Pakistan Creating WordPress websites for the clients

CERTIFICATES

Web Development Bootcamp

2022, Complete Web Development Bootcamp Certificate from Udemy.com

WordPress Certificate

2022. WordPress for Beginners course certificate from Udemy.com

WEB PROFILE

https://zeeshanmehmood59640.github.io/Profile/